myevent.com 2017-06-06

# Create Your Event Website - Fast and Easy

This privacy policy applies to www.myevent.com and www.websiteworks.com, owned and operated by MyEvent.com Inc. This privacy policy describes how MyEvent.com Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Websites. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

The visitors and the customers (the "User") of the MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com websites are in control of the use of information they provide to MyEvent.com, Websiteworks.com, or one of its current or future affiliate members ("Affiliate Members"). MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com are committed to respecting the privacy rights of Users to the MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com websites (the "Site"). 

While visiting the Site, we may ask Users to provide personal information ("Personal Information") for purposes of interacting with the Site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Please see the Effective Date stated at the conclusion of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and dissemination of information that we collect from Users. To the extent that Users disclose any such information to other parties, through other web sites on the Internet linked to this site or otherwise, THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL NOT APPLY TO SUCH DISCLOSURE. Since MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com do not control the privacy policies of third parties (including Affiliate Members), Users are subject to the privacy customs and policies, if any, of that third party, and MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of Personal Information by that third party. Therefore, we encourage Users to ask questions before they disclose Personal Information to other parties. 

#### Information Collected

These websites automatically collect and/or tracks various information, including but not limited to (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of web browser used to access the Site; (2) the e-mail addresses of Users that communicate with us via e-mail, or users that posted messages to the MyEvent.com bulletin boards, or users that post messages to MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com chat groups; (3) Personal Information specifically provided by the User in online forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests entries, and (4) user-specific information on what pages Users access. 

When registering through the website as on the order form or the free trial form, we provide the option for the user to "opt out" of any non-essential communications. These communications include newsletters, new product updates as well as special offers. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at info@myevent.com or at info@Websiteworks.com. We offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications through your Control Panel, or you may contact us at 514-282-7747, info@myevent.com or at info@Websiteworks.com or #305, 221 De La Commune ST W., Montreal, Quebec, H2Y 2C9 to opt-out. 

In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and/or create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at info@myevent.com or at info@Websiteworks.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com is the sole owner of the information collected on MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com. These websites collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

#### Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. We may also use this information to send you newsletters or updates on your account. Clients have the right to opt-out of non critical communications such as newsletters or new feature updates. Client's may not opt out of critical emails such as notifications of account status, or notification of account upgrades and/or account cancellations. 

#### Surveys or Contests

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). 

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

#### Cookies

A "cookie" is an element of data which is a piece of text, not a program and that a website can send to the User's browser, which may then be stored on a User's computer system. The Site can access the information from a cookie sent to a User's computer system. MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com does place cookies on Users' computer systems. MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com cannot access other cookies sent by other web sites or the information contained therein. We use cookies to track usage of the Site and further customize User's experience when such is visiting the Site. By tracking usage, MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com can best determine what features of the Site best serve each User. When a User revisits the Site, we will recognize such User by the cookie and may tailor her/his visit accordingly. Users may decline the cookie by using the appropriate feature of its web client software, if available, however, some functionality of the Site may not function properly if the User declines the cookie. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use a third-party live chat service called Liveperson that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate such as clickstream data in order to better serve our customers. We also use Google's keyword analytics to track clickstream data. 

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information. 

#### Remarketing

We only collect Personal Data from you, such as first and last name, phone number, e-mail, when you register to use our platform. We collect data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website or the websites and online services where we display advertisements. This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Remarketing”). We collect information about where you saw the ads we serve you and what ads you clicked on.

As you browse myevent.com/websitworks.com and other websites, online ad networks we work with may place anonymous cookies on your computer, and use similar technologies, in order to understand your interests based on your (anonymous) online activities, and thus to tailor more relevant ads to you. If you do not wish to receive such tailored advertising, you can visit this [page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to opt out of most companies that engage in such advertising. (This will not prevent you from seeing ads; the ads simply will not be delivered through these targeting methods.)

We do not target ads to you based on sensitive personal data, such as information related to race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs or other beliefs of a similar nature, trade union membership, physical or mental health or condition or sexual life. We may target ads based on data provided by Advertisers or partners alone or in combination with the data we collect ourselves. Any data used to serve targeted advertisements is de-identified and is not used to personally or directly identify you.

#### Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

#### Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

#### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

#### Information to Users

MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com reserves the right to use the Personal Information of Users to send them information via email about MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com, the Site, our products and services, and other topics or products, from these websites or others, in which such Users may have indicated interest. If a User prefers not to receive such messages, he/she may send an e-mail message to info@myevent.com or at info@Websiteworks.com with the subject "unsubscribe". MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com reserves the right to contact Users regarding accounts status and changes to the Terms of Use Agreement, this Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to the Site and/or to Users. 

#### Data Analysis & Other User

Personal Information collected by these websites either on a form or passively, will be used by MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com for general business purposes, including but not limited to editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many Users have seen or clicked on their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of the Site. 

#### Sharing of Personal Information

MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com will not sell, rent, swap, or otherwise disclose the registration data of Users to any unaffiliated third party. However, we may share Personal Information supplied by the User with Affiliate Members These Affiliate Members will not use this Personally Identifiable Information other than for the express purpose of providing the service(s) requested. For example, when Users reserve hotel rooms, car rental or airline tickets through MyEvent.com, we will provide information about such Users to the airline, car rental agency, hotel, travel agency or other involved third party to ensure the successful fulfillment of such arrangements. 

We may also disclose your personal information:

As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, if MyEvent.com or Websiteworks.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

We use other third parties to provide travel services on our site. When you sign up for Groople.com's travel services, we will share your name and email as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

#### Third Party Providers

MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com will from time to time contract with one or more third parties to maintain and host the Site, as well as provide Users with services related to its offering. Therefore, any information submitted by Users, including Personal Information, will be placed, stored and viewed on a computer server maintained by these third parties. The use of the Site by Users and any provision of Personal Information by same constitutes an irrevocable acknowledgement by such Users that such information or content could pass through and may be stored, accessed and used by third parties to process requests of such Users and in servers outside of the control of MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

#### No Liability for Acts of Third Parties

Although these websites will use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of Personal Information and/or the registration data, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com will have no liability for disclosure of registration data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [info@myevent.com](mailto:info@myevent.com "Click to mail to myevent.com") or at [info@Websiteworks.com](mailto:info@Websiteworks.com "Click to mail to Websiteworks.com")

#### Use of Aggregated Information

MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com reserves the right to disclose to third parties information about Users usage of the Site and any related services, including information gathered during use of the Site by Users. Any information disclosed will be in aggregate data form (such as overall patterns or demographic reports) that does not describe or identify any individual User. 

#### Access to Personal Information

Upon request via postal mail, or e-mail to [info@myevent.com](mailto:info@myevent.com "Click to mail to myevent.com") or [info@Websiteworks.com](mailto:info@Websiteworks.com "Click to mail to Websiteworks.com") with the subject "Access to Personal Information", MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com will provide Users with a summary of any of their Personal Information retained by these websites. Users may modify, correct, change or update their Personal Information or cause their Personal Information to be removed from the MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com database. MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com will only send Personal Information records to the e-mail address on file for the User name associated with it. 

#### Data Retention.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#### Children's Privacy

MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com does not specifically collect information about children, but is concerned about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical. 

#### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our Web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name, city and state. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting this personally identifiable information along with the testimonial. 

#### Updates.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 24, 2013. MyEvent.com and Websiteworks.com reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other MyEvent.com/Websiteworks.com policy or practice, at any time with reasonable notice to users of the Site. Any changes or updates will be effective upon posting to the Site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information unless you give us your consent to do otherwise. Your continued use of the Site following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes for future collections. 

#### Governing Law

This Privacy Policy and its performance shall be governed by the laws in force in the Province of Quebec, Canada. You consent and submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Province of Quebec, district of Montreal, in all questions and controversies arising out of your use of the Site and this Privacy Policy. 

MyEvent.com / Websiteworks.com  
#305 221 De La Commune St West  
Montreal, Quebec  
H2Y 2C9 

Effective Date: October 24, 2013
